{
 "data": [
    {
      "question": "The whole family had a great day at ______ Blenheim Palace.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Do not use \"the\" with the name of a place, for example a street, town, country, or airport \n- Do not use \"a/an\" when you mention a specific person or thing ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "14",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Paul met Lucy outside ______ Palace Theatre at eight o'clock.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Some places and countries, and all rivers and oceans, have the as part of their name",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "14",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The large park in the middle of New York is called ______ Central Park.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Do not use \"the\" with the name of a place, for example a street, town, country, or airport \n- Do not use \"a/an\" when you mention a specific person or thing ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "14",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The oldest glass in the world is from Egypt. It is in ______ British Museum, in London, and is nearly 3500 years old.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Some places and countries, and all rivers and oceans, have the as part of their name ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "14",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jason worked for the computer company ______ Microsoft for five years before starting his own software company.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Normally, Proper Noun doesn't take any article",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "14",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The only newspaper that the hotel has is ______ Washington Post. Do you want to read it?",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Some places and countries, and all rivers and oceans, have the as part of their name ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "14",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "______ Great Wall of China was begun in 221BC and is over 4500 miles long.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Some places and countries, and all rivers and oceans, have the as part of their name",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "14",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I always do my shopping at ______ Harrod's . It's the best department store in London.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Do not use \"the\" with the name of a place, for example a street, town, country, or airport\n- Do not use \"a/an\" when you mention a specific person or thing",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "14",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Tony and Ann spent a week at ______ Martinez Hotel in Cannes, France. It was the best holiday of their lives.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Some places and countries, and all rivers and oceans, have the as part of their name",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "14",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The oldest university in the world is ______ Al-Azhar University in Cairo, Egypt. Lessons began in 975AD.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Do not use \"the\" with the name of a place, for example a street, town, country, or airport \n- Do not use \"a/an\" when you mention a specific person or thing",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "14",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ] 
}